<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mindpeace</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="boatpose_desc">One of the most well-known yoga poses for core strength, Boat Pose - Navasana (nah-VAHS-uh-nuh)  tones the abdominal muscles while strengthening the low back</string>
    <string name="boatpose_benefits">Navasana deeply challenges the abdomen, spine, and hip flexors, building strength and steadiness at the body core. It stimulates the abdominal organs, including the kidneys and intestines, which improves digestion. This pose also encourages healthy regulation of the thyroid and prostate glands, helping to maintain metabolism and relieve stress.</string>
    <string name="bow_pose_benefits">This improves posture and spinal flexibility. Additionally, the pose helps to open the chest, abdomen, quadriceps, ankles, groins, hip flexors, and throat, Energizing and invigorating the body, mind, and spirit, Bow Pose also helps to relieve fatigue, stress, and anxiety</string>
    <string name="bowpose_desc">Dhanurasana (DAH-noo-RAH-suh-nuh) is an excellent back bending yoga pose for increasing and regaining spinal strength and flexibility. Dhanurasana also strengthens the leg muscles, especially the upper thighs, relieves stiff shoulders and reduces excess weight around the abdominal area.</string>
    <string name="cobrapose_desc">Cobra Pose  Bhujangasana (boo-jahn-GAHS-uh-nuh)  is a beginning backbend in yoga that helps to prepare the body for deeper backbends. Its name comes from the Sanskrit words, bhujanga and asana (meaning serpent and pose, respectively). Cobra is an essential element of Sun Salutations, and is an alternative to practicing Upward-Facing Dog (Urdhva Mukha Svanasana) in the Sun Salutations sequences.</string>
    <string name="cobrapose_ben">Cobra Pose is best known for its ability to increase the flexibility of the spine. It stretches the chest while strengthening the spine and shoulders. It also helps to open the lungs, which is therapeutic for asthma. This pose also stimulates the abdominal organs, improving digestion. An energizing backbend, Cobra reduces stress and fatigue. It also firms and tones the shoulders, abdomen, and buttocks, and helps to ease the pain of sciatica. Traditional yoga texts claim the pose heals the body of disease and awakens Kundalini  the divine cosmic energy that brings forth self-realization.</string>
    <string name="cresentpose_desc">Crescent Lunge  Anjaneyasana (AHN-jah-nay-AHS-uh-nuh)  is a dynamic standing yoga pose that utilizes and integrates the muscles in your entire body. It stretches and strengthens the lower and upper body, while creating stability and balance. Its name comes from the Sanskrit words anjaneya (meaning praise or salutation) and asana (meaning pose). Because of this, it is sometimes referred to as Salutation Pose, and it is performed many times during Sun Salutation C.</string>
    <string name="cresentpose_ben">Crescent Lunge stretches the legs, groin, and hip flexors, while also opening the front torso, chest, and shoulders. It strengthens and tones the thighs, hips, and butt, while the balancing aspect helps to develop flexible stability. Considered a balance pose, backbend, and heart opener, Crescent Lunge helps the front of the body to expand, which increases energy and reduces fatigue.</string>

    <string name="downward_facing_dog_desc">One of the most recognized yoga poses in the West, Downward-Facing Dog  Adho Mukha Svanasana (Ah-doh MOO-kuh shvan-AHS-uh-nuh) is a standing pose and mild inversion that builds strength while stretching the whole body. Its named after the way dogs naturally stretch their entire bodies Downward-Facing Dog (also sometimes called Downward Dog or just Down Dog) is an essential component of Sun Salutations and is often done many times during a yoga class. It can be used as a transitional pose, a resting pose, and a strength-builder.</string>
    <string name="downward_facing_dog_ben">Downward-Facing Dog energizes and rejuvenates the entire body. It deeply stretches your hamstrings, shoulders, calves, arches, hands, and spine while building strength in your arms, shoulders, and legs. Because your heart is higher than your head in this pose, it is considered a mild inversion (less strenuous than other inversions, such as Headstand) and holds all the benefits of inversions: Relief from headaches, insomnia, fatigue, and mild depression. The flow of blood to the brain also calms the nervous system, improves memory and concentration, and relieves stress.Regular practice of this pose can improve digestion, relieve back pain, and help prevent osteoporosis. It is also known to be therapeutic for sinusitis, asthma, flat feet, and for the symptoms of menopause.</string>

    <string name="easy_pose_desc">Easy Pose  Sukhasana (soo-KAHS-uh-nuh) is a basic seated yoga posture. It is depicted in some of the oldest images of ancient yogis in India, some of which are at least 2,000 years old. Also sometimes called Simple Cross-Legged Pose, Sukhasana is intended to be comfortable and calming.</string>
    <string name="easy_pose_ben">Sukhasana strengthens the back and stretches the knees and ankles. It also opens the hips, groin, and outer thigh muscles (abductors). Sitting upright with your spine aligned also reduces stress and anxiety. It calms the mind and is known to be therapeutic for stress.</string>

    <string name="half_pigeon_desc">Ardha Kapotasana is derived from the Sanskrit word, kapota, meaning pigeon and asana, meaning posture.This simple first stage of Half Pigeon Pose, is considered as an Intermediate Level Pose, which requires some flexibility at the hips and back. The stretching of the chest upwards in this pose, resembles a pigeon puffing up its chest and hence the comparison.Seated on the floor with one leg extended backwards and the other leg is bent at the knee placed in front of you, you are balancing the body on the that side of the hip which has the leg bent at the knee. A deep stretch to the entire hip and the back.</string>
    <string name="half_pigeon_ben">At the practice of the full Pigeon Pose, the entire piriformis muscles are stretched to the maximum, and in this simple Pigeon Pose the piriformis muscles are stretched slowly,plays a great role in building the flexibility of the hips.</string>

    <string name="lowlunge_desc">Anjaneyasana (Crescent Low Lunge Pose) gets its name after Lord Hanumans mother named Anjani. This pose is performed by stretching one leg behind and placing the other one in front with knee bent and foot on the floor. The arms are raised up with palms joined in Namaste and expanding the chest and stretching the neck. This yoga pose is also called Low Lunge as the shin and part of the thighs for the stretched leg are rested on the floor.</string>
    <string name="lowlunge_ben">In Anjaneyasana (Crescent Low Lunge Pose), the deep stretch of the neck, with a gentle throw of the head backwards, stretches the muscles around the neck region close to the thyroid gland. The stretching of these muscles activates and stimulates the thyroid gland which controls the overall metabolism of the human body.taking the chest forward and upward enables the muscles around the heart to open deeper, creating a better flow of breath or prana which then brings a good circulation of blood.</string>

    <string name="upward_bow_desc">Upward Bow Pose (Urdhva Dhanurasana) is an advanced yoga pose that stretches and opens the entire body. It is sometimes considered the peak backbend, so it is often practiced toward the end of class when the body is warm and open.</string>
    <string name="upward_bow_ben">This pose stretches the spine, shoulders, chest, upper back, and thighs. It also strengthens the arms, wrists, spine, legs, and abdomen. The deep back-bending aspect of this pose opens the lungs, which makes it therapeutic for asthma. Additionally, this pose stimulates the thyroid and pituitary glands, increasing energy and providing relief from mild depression.</string>

    <string name="warrior_pose_desc">Warrior II  Virabhadrasana II (veer-uh-buh-DRAHS-uh-nuh)  is a standing yoga pose that enhances strength, stability, and concentration. Its named after the Hindu mythological warrior, Virabhadra, an incarnation of the god Shiva. Virabhadra was a tall, dark, and fierce deity, depicted with a thousand arms, flaming hair and eyes, and wearing a garland of skulls.</string>
    <string name="warrior_pose_ben">A powerful stretch for the legs, groins, and chest, Virabhadrasana II also increases stamina. It helps to relieve backaches, and stimulates healthy digestion.This is a deep hip-opening pose that strengthens the muscles in the thighs and buttocks. It tones the abdomen, ankles, and arches of the feet. This pose also opens the chest and shoulders, improving breathing capacity and increasing circulation throughout the body. It is also known to be therapeutic for flat feet, sciatica, infertility, and osteoporosis.</string>

    <string name="warrior_pose2_desc">This pose, called Virabhadrasana III (veer-uh-buh-DRAHS-uh-nuh) in Sanskrit, is named after the mythological Hindu warrior, Virabhadra. A tall, dark, and powerful incarnation of the god Shiva, Virabhadra is depicted with a thousand heads, a thousand arms, and a thousand flaming eyes. He embodies the fierce power required of a warrior. Practicing Virabhadrasana III will enhance your own power by building inner and outer strength, stability, and concentration.</string>
    <string name="warrior_pose2_ben">Warrior III strengthens the whole back side of the body, including the shoulders, hamstrings, calves, ankles, and back. It also tones and strengthens the abdominal muscles. Warrior III improves balance, posture, and full-body coordination.</string>

</resources>
